(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{21:function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},47:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(60)},52:function(e,t,a){},60:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),o=a(14),i=a.n(o),c=(a(52),a(9)),s=a(35),l=a(77),u=a(80),m=a(81),d=a(82),f=a(27),h=a(79),y=a(86),p=a(83);function g(e){return r.a.createElement(p.a,{display:"flex",alignItems:"center"},r.a.createElement(p.a,{width:"100%",mr:1},r.a.createElement(y.a,Object.assign({variant:"determinate"},e))),r.a.createElement(p.a,{minWidth:35},r.a.createElement(f.a,{variant:"body2",color:"textSecondary"},"".concat(Math.round(e.value),"%"))))}var w=Object(l.a)({progress:{margin:"auto",width:"90%"}});function E(e){var t=e.questionNumber,a=e.totalQuestions,n=w(),o=r.a.useState(10),i=Object(c.a)(o,2),s=i[0],l=i[1];return r.a.useEffect(function(){l(100*(1==t?0:t/a))},[t]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:n.progress},r.a.createElement(g,{value:s}))}var b=a(78);function v(e){return r.a.createElement(p.a,{position:"relative",display:"inline-flex"},r.a.createElement(b.a,Object.assign({variant:"determinate"},e)),r.a.createElement(p.a,{top:0,left:0,bottom:0,right:0,position:"absolute",display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},r.a.createElement(f.a,{variant:"caption",component:"div",color:"textSecondary"},"".concat(Math.round(e.value),"%"))))}function _(e){var t=e.score,a=e.totalQuestions,n=e.questionNumber,o=r.a.useState(10),i=Object(c.a)(o,2),s=i[0],l=i[1];return r.a.useEffect(function(){l(1===n?100:Math.floor((a-t)/a*100))},[n]),r.a.createElement(v,{value:s})}function S(e){return r.a.createElement(p.a,{position:"relative",display:"inline-flex"},r.a.createElement(b.a,Object.assign({variant:"determinate"},e)),r.a.createElement(p.a,{top:0,left:0,bottom:0,right:0,position:"absolute",display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},r.a.createElement(f.a,{variant:"caption",component:"div",color:"textSecondary"},"".concat(Math.round(e.value),"%"))))}function x(e){var t=e.score,a=e.totalQuestions,n=r.a.useState(10),o=Object(c.a)(n,2),i=o[0],s=o[1];return r.a.useEffect(function(){s(t/a*100)},[t]),r.a.createElement(S,{value:i})}var C=Object(l.a)({root:{width:"100%"}});function q(e){var t=e.score,a=e.totalQuestions,n=e.questionNumber,o=C(),i=r.a.useState(0),s=Object(c.a)(i,2),l=s[0],u=s[1],m=r.a.useState(10),d=Object(c.a)(m,2),f=d[0],h=d[1];r.a.useRef(function(){});return r.a.useEffect(function(){u(t/a*100),h((a-t)/a*100)},[n]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:o.root},r.a.createElement(y.a,{variant:"buffer",value:l,valueBuffer:f}))}var N=Object(l.a)(function(e){return{btn:{flex:1,padding:10,margin:5,maxWidth:400}}}),W=function(e){var t=e.options,a=e.optionsHandler,n=N();return r.a.createElement("div",null,t.map(function(e){return r.a.createElement(h.a,{className:n.btn,variant:"contained",color:"secondary",onClick:function(){return a(e)},key:e},decodeURIComponent(e))}))},A=a(29),H=a(33),j=a(34),F=function(e){var t=new Array(5),a=r.a.createElement(A.a,{icon:H.a}),n=r.a.createElement(A.a,{icon:j.a});switch(e){case"easy":return t.fill(a,0,1).fill(n,1,5);case"medium":return t.fill(a,0,2).fill(n,2,5);case"hard":return t.fill(a,0,3).fill(n,3,5);default:return null}},O=a(84),k=Object(l.a)(function(e){return{root:{width:"100%","& > * + *":{marginTop:e.spacing(2)}}}}),B=function(e){var t=e.status,a=k();return r.a.createElement("div",{className:a.root},null!=t&&"Correct Answer"==t?r.a.createElement(O.a,{severity:"success"},"Correct Answer \u2014 Great Success!"):"Sorry!"==t?r.a.createElement(O.a,{severity:"warning"},"Sorry \u2014 Wrong Answer :"):null,r.a.createElement("br",null))},M=Object(l.a)(function(e){return{root:{margin:"auto",marginTop:"2vh",display:"flex",flexFlow:"column",minWidth:400,maxWidth:800,minHeight:300},content:{textAlign:"center"},btncontainer:{flex:1,textAlign:"center",flexDirection:"row",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center"},question:{marginLeft:80,fontSize:18,fontWeight:"bold"},bottomContainer:{display:"flex",flexFlow:"row"},scoreProgress:{alignSelf:"flex-start"},maxScoreProgress:{marginLeft:"auto",alignSelf:"flex-end"}}});function Q(e){var t=e.questionNumber,a=e.nextHandler,n=e.question,o=e.totalQuestions,i=e.optionsHandler,c=e.status,l=e.score,y=M(),p="Question ".concat(t," of ").concat(o);return r.a.createElement(u.a,{className:y.root},r.a.createElement(E,{questionNumber:t,totalQuestions:o}),r.a.createElement(m.a,{className:y.content,title:p}),r.a.createElement(m.a,{className:y.content,title:decodeURIComponent(n.category),subheader:"Category"}),r.a.createElement(m.a,{className:y.content,title:F(n.difficulty),subheader:"Difficulty"}),r.a.createElement(d.a,null,r.a.createElement(f.a,{className:y.question,paragraph:!0},"Question:"),r.a.createElement(f.a,{className:y.content,paragraph:!0},decodeURIComponent(n.question))),r.a.createElement(d.a,{className:y.btncontainer},r.a.createElement(W,{optionsHandler:i,options:[].concat(Object(s.a)(n.incorrect_answers),[n.correct_answer])})),r.a.createElement(d.a,{className:y.btncontainer},r.a.createElement(B,{status:c}),r.a.createElement(h.a,{variant:"contained",color:"secondary",onClick:a},"Next")),r.a.createElement(d.a,{className:y.bottomContainer},r.a.createElement(d.a,{className:y.scoreProgress},"Score:"),r.a.createElement(x,{totalQuestions:o,score:l,className:y.scoreProgress}),r.a.createElement(d.a,{className:y.maxScoreProgress},"Max Score:"),r.a.createElement(_,{questionNumber:t,totalQuestions:o,score:l,className:y.maxScoreProgress})),r.a.createElement(d.a,null,r.a.createElement(q,{questionNumber:t,totalQuestions:o,score:l})))}var T=a(21),I=Object(l.a)({root:{marginTop:"25vh",margin:"auto",maxWidth:400},title:{fontSize:14},pos:{marginBottom:12}});function P(e){var t=e.restartQuiz,a=I();return r.a.createElement(u.a,{className:a.root},r.a.createElement(d.a,null,r.a.createElement(f.a,{variant:"h5",component:"h2"},"Thank you for taking the Quiz!"),r.a.createElement(f.a,{className:a.pos,color:"textSecondary"},"Press restart to retake the Quiz"),r.a.createElement(h.a,{onClick:t,variant:"contained",color:"secondary"},"Restart")))}var D=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(0),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),a=t[0],o=t[1],i=Object(n.useState)(0),s=Object(c.a)(i,2),l=s[0],u=s[1],m=Object(n.useState)(!1),d=Object(c.a)(m,2),f=d[0],h=d[1],y=Object(n.useState)(null),p=Object(c.a)(y,2),g=p[0],w=p[1];return f?r.a.createElement(P,{restartQuiz:function(){u(0),h(!1),o(0),w(null)}}):r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(Q,{questionNumber:a+1,totalQuestions:T.length,question:T[a],optionsHandler:function(e){null!==g?alert("You have already answered"):e===T[a].correct_answer?(u(function(e){return e+1}),w("Correct Answer")):w("Sorry!")},nextHandler:function(){null===g?alert("Please select an option."):void 0!==T[a+1]?(o(function(e){return e+1}),w(null)):h(!0)},status:g,score:l}))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(r.a.createElement(D,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}},[[47,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.fa4137a1.chunk.js.map